A Finding Aid to the Violet Oakley Papers, 1841-1981, in the Archives of American Art AAA.oaklviol
Archives of American Art
Violet Oakley papers
1841-1981
AAA.oaklviol
Archives of American Art
57.4 Linear feet
The papers of painter, stained glass artist, and muralist Violet Oakley measure 57.4 linear feet and date from 1841-1981. Found within the papers are biographical materials; personal and business correspondence; writings, including essays, lectures, and project drafts; diaries and journals; financial material; artwork; printed material, including scrapbooks; and photographs, 3 albums, 322 glass plate negatives, and 1600 film negatives of Oakley, her family and friends, and her work.
Oakley, Violet, 1874-1961
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The papers were donated in 1977 and 1984 by Oakley's longtime friend and companion, Edith Emerson. In 1988, two additional feel of materials were donated by the Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, who had received the papers from Emerson's estate.
Separated Materials note
Originals of material loaned for microfilming, which consist of Violet Oakley's scrapbooks containing press clippings, correspondence, programs, invitations, reproductions of artwork, and ephemera dating from 1896 to 1962, as well as a family photograph album and photographs of artwork, were returned to Edith Emerson. Loaned material is still available on reels 1204, P12, 1187-1188, 1272, and 1194-1195 but is not included in the container listing of this finding aid.
Reel 1204 consists of two scrapbooks (circa 1896-1952) containing clippings from magazines of illustrations by Violet Oakley and her sister, Hester, and of Violet's murals for the State Capitol at Harrisburg, Pennsylvania. Reel P12 is of a scrapbook (1898-1936) containing a photograph of Oakely at her easel, clippings, and letters. Reels 1187-1188 consist of five scrapbooks (1920-1962) containing letters, clippings, exhibition announcements, catalogs, and awards. One of the scrapbooks is devoted to "The Holy Experiment", a limited edition publication by Oakley which commemorating William Penn, and which includes reproductions of Oakley's capitol murals in Harrisburg.
Reel 1272 consists of two albums (circa 1900-1949) containing photos of Oakley working on murals in her studio, as well as her works of art, including stained glass windows at the Church of All Angels, New York; murals at the Harrisburg State Capitol; preliminary drawings and site photographs of "Dante's Window"; the lunettes and window for the Yarnall House; murals and preliminary drawings for the Cuyahoga Court House; the mural and dedication ceremonies for the Vassar Alumnae House; and photos and printed material on "Divine Presence--Christ at Geneva," "The Life of Moses," "Great Women of the Bible," and triptychs for the Army and Navy.
Reels 1194-1195 consist of photograph albums (circa 1870-1960) containing photographs of the Oakley and Swain families, of Violet Oakley, Edith Emerson, Jessie Willcox Smith, Elizabeth Shippen Green, friends, her home, Oakley's "Red Rose" studio in Villanova, Pennsylvania, her "Cogslea" studio in Philadelphia, and of her works of art, mainly portraits of her friends and of delegates to the League of Nations.
Related Archival Materials note
Also found among the holdings of the Archives of American Art are the Violet Oakley Memorial Foundation records and the Violet Oakley autograph and photograph. The Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts holds the Violet Oakley Foundation Art Collection, and the Philadelphia Museum of Art holds the Violet Oakley Collection.
Existence and Location of Copies note
The bulk of the correspondence in this collection is available on 35 mm microfilm reels 3716-3745 at the Archives of American Art offices, and through interlibrary loan. Researchers should note that the arrangement of the papers as described in this finding aid does not reflect the order of the collection on microfilm due to reprocessing.
Conditions Governing Access note
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' research center in Washington, D.C. Glass plate negatives are housed separately and closed to researchers.
Biographical/Historical note
Painter, muralist, and stained glass designer Violet Oakley (1874-1961) lived and worked in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania and was known for her Renaissance-revival style of art and the series of murals she completed for the Pennsylvania State Capitol.
Born in Bergen Heights, New Jersey, to a family of artists, both of Violet Oakley's grandfathers were painters and members of the National Academy. In 1892, she began her art studies at the Art Students' League and traveled abroad a year later to study in Paris at the Academie Montparnasse, and in England with Charles Lazar. Upon her return to the states in 1896, she continued her studies at the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, and at Drexel Institute with Howard Pyle.
For fourteen years, Oakley shared her early studios at Red Rose Inn and Cogslea Estate with fellow artists and illustrators Elizabeth Shippen Green and Jessie Willcox Smith. These two studio homes were managed by their friend Henrietta Cozens in a cooperative arrangement which allowed all three artists to focus on their work as commercial artists. Early in her career, Oakley designed covers for magazines such as Collier's Weekly and Century Magazine, and also found work as a stained glass designer for the Church Glass and Decorating Company of New York. In 1900, she received her first major commission to design and execute two large murals and six stained glass pieces for the All Angels' Church in New York City.
In 1902 Oakley was approached by architect Joseph Huston to design 13 murals for the Governor's reception room in the new Pennsylvania State Capitol in Harrisburg. She eventually completed two additional mural commissions for the Capitol's Senate (1911-1920) and Supreme Court (1917-1927) chambers. Her studies of William Penn in connection with her murals for the State Capitol inspired Oakley to work for international peace and eventually led to the publication of a portrait folio depicting League of Nations delegates (1932). Other significant works include murals, panels, and stained glass commissions completed for the Vassar College Alumni house, Charlton Yarnall house (Philadelphia), and Cuyuhoga County courthouse.
While working as an established artist, Oakley also taught courses at the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, arranged a yearly lecture series, and published folios and other writings on topics ranging from art history to Christian Science under the Coslea Studios imprint. Her later studio, Lower Cogslea, was shared by artist and lifelong companion Edith Emerson, who after Oakley's death in 1961, established a memorial foundation in her name.
Oakley was the first woman elected to the National Society of Mural Painters, was a recipient of the Gold Medal of Honor of the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, and was the first woman to receive the Gold Medal of Honor from the Architectural League of New York. Her writings include The Holy Experiment: A Message to the World from Pennsylvania (1922) and Law Triumphant: The Opening of the Book of Law (1933).
Scope and Contents note
The papers of painter, stained glass artist, and muralist Violet Oakley measure 57.4 linear feet and date from 1841-1981. Found within the papers are biographical materials; personal and business correspondence; writings, including essays, lectures, and project drafts; diaries and journals; financial material; artwork; printed material, including scrapbooks; and photographs, 3 albums, 322 glass plate negatives, and 1600 film negatives of Oakley, her family and friends, and her work.
Biographical materials include certificates, family records, curriculum vitae, and identification cards, and studio guest books. About one-half of the collection is comprised of correspondence with family, friends, and business associates. Writings include Oakley's notes, essays and lectures, and writings related to 16 of her major artworks and publications, including her work on the Pennsylvania Capitol murals in Harrisburg. Diaries and journals include Oakley's travel notes and research on planned artworks.
Financial materials include a catalog of artworks and price lists, accounting records, and art supply receipts. Artwork includes early childhood juvenilia, a sketchbook, sketches of travel and friends, architectural renderings, and artwork by others. Printed materials include books, clippings, exhibition catalogs, programs, and reproductions of artwork by Oakley and others. Photographic materials include photographs, albums, and negatives depicting Oakley, her friends and family, her studio at Cogslea, and reproductions of artwork.
Arrangement note
The collection is arranged as 8 series. A comprehensive index of individidual correspondents for the chronological correspondence is found in the first folder of the chronological correspondence in box 5, folder 41. Glass plate negatives are housed separately and closed to researchers, but listed where they fall intellectually within the collection.
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1841-1970 (2.8 linear feet; Boxes 1-3, OV 69, OV 71)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1857-1979 (26.7 linear feet; Boxes 3-30)
Series 3: Notes and Writings, 1899-1976 (10.6 linear feet; Boxes 30-38, 58-64, OV 66, OV 70)
Series 4: Diaries and Journals, 1891-1958 (0.9 linear feet, Boxes 38-39)
Series 5: Financial Material, 1874-1977 (3.1 linear feet; Boxes 39-42)
Series 6: Artwork, 1883-1955 (0.7 linear feet; Boxes 43-43, 64, OV 67, OV 71)
Series 7: Printed Material, 1866-1981 (7.3 linear feet, Boxes 43-50, 65, OV 67)
Series 8: Photographs, 1890-1980 (5.3 linear feet; Boxes 50-57, 65, OV 68)
Pennsylvania State Capitol. (Harrisburg, Pa.); Artists' materials; Artists' studios--Photographs; Diaries; Glass plate negatives; Mural painting and decoration--United States; Muralists--Pennsylvania--Philadelphia; Painters--Pennsylvania--Philadelphia; Photographs; Renderings; Scrapbooks; Sketchbooks; Sketches; Stained glass artists--Pennsylvania--Philadelphia; Visitors books; Women artists--Pennsylvania--Philadelphia
- Biographical Materials, 1841-1970; Series 1; 2.8 Linear feet Boxes 1-3, OV 69, 71
  Arrangement note
  The majority of materials are arranged by document type. The latter part of the series groups calendars, studio guest books, and other documents relating to Oakley's extended family.
  Scope and Contents note
  Biographical materials include address books, award certificates, curriculum vitae, calendars, identification and membership cards, memorabilia, genealogical research, and Cogslea estate guest/visitor books. The guest books include the dates, signatures, and salutations of visitors to Oakley's studios, including the shared studio space of Violet Oakley, Elizabeth Shippen Green, and Jessie Willcox Smith during the 1910s-1920s. In addition to monthly calendars, there are Line-a-Day calendars for 1924, 1929, 1935-1939, 1941 and daybook calendars for 1937, 1941, 1946.
  - Address Card File, circa 1920-1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Address Books, circa 1920-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2-7)
  - Address Books, circa 1920-1960 (Box 1, Folder 8-12)
  - Baptism Certificate, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Biographical Notes and Addenda, circa 1931 (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
  - Biographical Notes and Curriculum Vitae, circa 1950-1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Biographical Notes, circa 1950-1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Card, Identity, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cards, Membership and Permission, 1895-1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Certificate of Appreciation, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Certificate of Award, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Certificate of Merit, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Certificates, circa 1920-1950 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Oversize material housed in OV 69 and 71.
  - Honorary Degree, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Objects, Buttons and Medals, circa 1920-1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Object, Funerary Fabric, circa 1920-1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Object, Leather Diary Cover, circa 1920-1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Object, Leather Journal Cover, circa 1920-1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Objects, Medallions and Wax Seals, circa 1920-1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Passport, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Calendars, circa 1925-1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Calendars, 1924-1933 (Box 2, Folder 9-18)
  - Calendars, 1934-1940 (Box 2, Folder 19-27)
  - Calendars, 1941-1960 (Box 2, Folder 28-38)
  - Guest Book, 1913-1924 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Guest Books, 1913-1938 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Guest Books, 1930-1955 (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  - Oakley Children, Dates of Birth, 1875 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Oakley Family Index and Genealogy Research, 1958-1970 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - Oakley, Cornelia, Baby Teeth, circa 1870-1880 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Oakley, Cornelia, Address Book, 1908, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
  - Oakley, Cornelia, Calendar, 1884-1888 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - Oakley, Hester, 1891-1894 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Oakley, Nelson, Estate Settlement, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Swain, Paul M., Passport, 1872 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Swain, William, Passport, 1841-1843 (Box 3, Folder 18-20)
  - Emerson, Edith, Calendar, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Oversize Certificates from Box 1, Folder 23, circa 1920-1950 (Box OV 69, OV 71)
- Correspondence, 1857-1979; Series 2; 26.7 Linear feet Boxes 3-30
  A small selection of letters are arranged alphabetically by sender. The remaining correspondence is arranged in chronological order. A comprehensive index of individidual correspondents for the chronological correspondence is found in the first folder of the chronological correspondence in box 5, folder 41.
  Early correspondence dating from 1857 to 1894 is primarily between Oakley family members. Later incoming and outgoing correspondence dating from 1895 onwards is between Violet Oakley and her friends, artists, business associates, and after her death, those people interested in the functions sponsored by the Violet Oakley Memorial Foundation through Edith Emerson. Some letters contain enclosures such as photographs, writings, and contracts.
  - A, circa 1890-1960 (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
  - B, circa 1890-1960 (Box 3, Folder 24-33)
  - C, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
  - D, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 6-9)
  - E, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 10-12)
  - F, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
  - G, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
  - H, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 17-20)
  - I, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - J, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 22-23)
  - K, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - L, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 25-27)
  - M, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 28-35)
  - N, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 36-38)
  - O, circa 1890-1960 (Box 4, Folder 39-44)
  - P, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
  - Q, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - R, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
  - S, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 8-16)
  - T, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 17-21)
  - U, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - V, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - W, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 24-30)
  - X-Z, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Writers Unknown, First Name Only, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 32-38)
  - Writers Unknown, circa 1890-1960 (Box 5, Folder 39-40)
  - Chronological, 1857-1879 (Box 5, Folder 41-47)
  - Chronological, 1880-1886 (Box 5, Folder 48-52)
  - Chronological, 1887-1890 (Box 6, Folder 1-10)
  - Chronological, 1891-1893 (Box 6, Folder 11-21)
  - Chronological, 1894-1896 (Box 6, Folder 22-32)
  - Chronological, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 33-41)
  - Chronological, 1898-1900 (Box 7, Folder 1-7)
  - Chronological, 1901-1902 (Box 7, Folder 8-17)
  - Chronological, 1903-1904 (Box 7, Folder 18-29)
  - Chronological, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 30-42)
  - Chronological, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 43-50)
  - Chronological, 1907-1908 (Box 7, Folder 51-57)
  - Chronological, 1909-1910 (Box 8, Folder 1-9)
  - Chronological, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 10-21)
  - Chronological, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 22-33)
  - Chronological, 1913, January-June (Box 8, Folder 34-41)
  - Chronological, 1913, July-December (Box 8, Folder 42-49)
  - Chronological, 1914, January-March (Box 8, Folder 50-53)
  - Chronological, 1914, April-December (Box 9, Folder 1-13)
  - Chronological, 1915, January-February (Box 9, Folder 14-24)
  - Chronological, 1915, March-September (Box 9, Folder 25-35)
  - Chronological, 1915, October-December (Box 9, Folder 36-48)
  - Chronological, 1916, January-April (Box 9, Folder 49-54)
  - Chronological, 1916, May-September (Box 10, Folder 1-8)
  - Chronological, 1916, October-December (Box 10, Folder 9-16)
  - Chronological, 1917, January-April (Box 10, Folder 17-23)
  - Chronological, 1917, May 1-4 (Box 10, Folder 24-31)
  - Chronological, 1917, May 5-31 (Box 10, Folder 32-39)
  - Chronological, 1917, June-December (Box 10, Folder 40-45)
  - Chronological, 1918, January-July (Box 10, Folder 46-52)
  - Chronological, 1918, August-December (Box 10, Folder 53-58)
  - Chronological, 1919, January-April (Box 10, Folder 59-63)
  - Chronological, 1919, May-December (Box 11, Folder 1-10)
  - Chronological, 1920, January-June (Box 11, Folder 11-19)
  - Chronological, 1920, July-December (Box 11, Folder 20-29)
  - Chronological, 1921, January-June (Box 11, Folder 30-36)
  - Chronological, 1921, July-December (Box 11, Folder 37-43)
  - Chronological, 1922, January-May (Box 11, Folder 44-51)
  - Chronological, 1922, June-August (Box 11, Folder 52-57)
  - Chronological, 1922, September-October (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
  - Chronological, 1922, November (Box 12, Folder 6-16)
  - Chronological, 1922, December (Box 12, Folder 17-22)
  - Chronological, 1923, January-May (Box 12, Folder 23-33)
  - Chronological, 1923, June-July (Box 12, Folder 34-45)
  - Chronological, 1923, August-December (Box 12, Folder 46-52)
  - Chronological, 1924, January-April (Box 13, Folder 1-11)
  - Chronological, 1924, May-December (Box 13, Folder 12-24)
  - Chronological, 1925, January-May (Box 13, Folder 25-35)
  - Chronological, 1925, June-December (Box 13, Folder 36-47)
  - Chronological, 1926, January (Box 13, Folder 48-52)
  - Chronological, 1926, February-April (Box 14, Folder 1-11)
  - Chronological, 1926, May-July (Box 14, Folder 12-21)
  - Chronological, 1926, August-October (Box 14, Folder 22-31)
  - Chronological, 1926, November (Box 14, Folder 32-41)
  - Chronological, 1926, December (Box 14, Folder 42-44)
  - Chronological, 1927, January-March (Box 14, Folder 45-53)
  - Chronological, 1927, April-July (Box 15, Folder 1-10)
  - Chronological, 1927, August-December (Box 15, Folder 11-19)
  - Chronological, 1928-1929 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Letterbook
  - Chronological, 1928, January-July (Box 15, Folder 21-31)
  - Chronological, 1928, August-December (Box 15, Folder 32-39)
  - Chronological, 1929, January (Box 15, Folder 40-41)
  - Chronological, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Chronological, 1929, February-June (Box 15, Folder 43-50)
  - Chronological, 1929, July-September (Box 16, Folder 1-12)
  - Chronological, 1929, October-December (Box 16, Folder 13-22)
  - Chronological, 1930, January-February (Box 16, Folder 23-34)
  - Chronological, 1930, March-June (Box 16, Folder 35-45)
  - Chronological, 1930-1932 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Chronological, 1930, July-October (Box 16, Folder 47-53)
  - Chronological, 1930, November-December (Box 17, Folder 1-6)
  - Chronological, 1931, January-April (Box 17, Folder 7-15)
  - Chronological, 1931, May-August (Box 17, Folder 16-25)
  - Chronological, 1931, September-December (Box 17, Folder 26-33)
  - Chronological, 1932, January-March (Box 17, Folder 34-41)
  - Chronological, 1932, April-September (Box 17, Folder 42-52)
  - Chronological, 1932, October-December (Box 17, Folder 53-62)
  - Chronological, 1933, January-May (Box 18, Folder 1-12)
  - Chronological, 1933, June-August (Box 18, Folder 13-19)
  - Chronological, 1933, September-December (Box 18, Folder 20-25)
  - Chronological, 1934, January-June (Box 18, Folder 26-33)
  - Chronological, 1934, July-December (Box 18, Folder 34-42)
  - Chronological, 1935, January-May (Box 18, Folder 43-51)
  - Chronological, 1935, June-December (Box 19, Folder 1-9)
  - Chronological, 1936, January-May (Box 19, Folder 10-19)
  - Chronological, 1936, June-August (Box 19, Folder 20-27)
  - Chronological, 1936, September-October (Box 19, Folder 28-35)
  - Chronological, 1936, November-December (Box 19, Folder 36-41)
  - Chronological, 1937, January-March (Box 19, Folder 42-48)
  - Chronological, 1937, April-July (Box 20, Folder 1-9)
  - Chronological, 1937, August-December (Box 20, Folder 10-16)
  - Chronological, 1938, January-June (Box 20, Folder 17-26)
  - Chronological, 1938, July-December (Box 20, Folder 27-37)
  - Chronological, 1939, January-April (Box 20, Folder 38-50)
  - Chronological, 1939, May-June (Box 21, Folder 1-10)
  - Chronological, 1939, July-October (Box 21, Folder 11-20)
  - Chronological, 1939, November-December (Box 21, Folder 21-25)
  - Chronological, 1940, January-February (Box 21, Folder 26-34)
  - Chronological, 1940, March-May (Box 21, Folder 35-46)
  - Chronological, 1940, June-December (Box 22, Folder 1-10)
  - Chronological, 1941, January-March (Box 22, Folder 11-19)
  - Chronological, 1941, April-September (Box 22, Folder 20-28)
  - Chronological, 1941, October-December (Box 22, Folder 29-35)
  - Chronological, 1942, January-May (Box 22, Folder 36-46)
  - Chronological, 1942, June-December (Box 22, Folder 47-58)
  - Chronological, 1943, January-July (Box 23, Folder 1-10)
  - Chronological, 1943, August-December (Box 23, Folder 11-20)
  - Chronological, 1944, January-April (Box 23, Folder 21-31)
  - Chronological, 1944, May-December (Box 23, Folder 32-43)
  - Chronological, 1945, January-July (Box 23, Folder 44-54)
  - Chronological, 1945, August-December (Box 24, Folder 1-9)
  - Chronological, 1946, January-June (Box 24, Folder 10-21)
  - Chronological, 1946, July-December (Box 24, Folder 22-34)
  - Chronological, 1947, January-May (Box 24, Folder 35-44)
  - Chronological, 1947, June-December (Box 24, Folder 45-56)
  - Chronological, 1948, January-June (Box 25, Folder 1-12)
  - Chronological, 1948, July-December (Box 25, Folder 13-22)
  - Chronological, 1949, January-May (Box 25, Folder 23-32)
  - Chronological, 1949, June-December (Box 25, Folder 33-41)
  - Chronological, 1950, January-August (Box 25, Folder 42-53)
  - Chronological, 1950, September-December (Box 26, Folder 1-9)
  - Chronological, 1951, January-June (Box 26, Folder 10-20)
  - Chronological, 1951, July-December (Box 26, Folder 21-30)
  - Chronological, 1952, January-June (Box 26, Folder 31-41)
  - Chronological, 1952, July-October (Box 26, Folder 42-48)
  - Chronological, 1952, November-December (Box 27, Folder 1-5)
  - Chronological, 1953, January-April (Box 27, Folder 6-15)
  - Chronological, 1953, May (Box 27, Folder 16-24)
  - Chronological, 1953, June-August (Box 27, Folder 25-35)
  - Chronological, 1953, September-December (Box 27, Folder 36-48)
  - Chronological, 1954, January-June (Box 28, Folder 1-10)
  - Chronological, 1954, July-December (Box 28, Folder 11-21)
  - Chronological, 1955, January-June (Box 28, Folder 22-31)
  - Chronological, 1955, July-December (Box 28, Folder 32-38)
  - Chronological, 1956, January-September (Box 28, Folder 39-47)
  - Chronological, 1956, October-December (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
  - Chronological, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Letter register.
  - Chronological, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 5-17)
  - Chronological, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 18-26)
  - Chronological, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 27-31)
  - Chronological, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 32-33)
    Birthday greetings.
  - Chronological, 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 34-44)
  - Chronological, 1966-1968 (Box 29, Folder 45-51)
  - Chronological, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 1-9)